<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Octagon</string>
    <string name="facebook_key">1782994848601305</string>
    <string name="status_bar_title">The Octagon Project</string>

    <!--Login Screen-->
    <string name="login_status">The Entire Holy Land in Virtual Reality!</string>
    <string name="login_ways">There are two ways to login.</string>
    <string name="way_facebook">1. Through your Facebook account.</string>
    <string name="way_username">2. Use your registered Octagon Project username and password.</string>
    <string name="text_username">Username (case sensitive)</string>
    <string name="text_password">Password (case sensitive)</string>
    <string name="remember_me">Remember Me</string>
    <string name="text_forgot">Forgot your username or password?</string>
    <string name="login">Log In</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="error_username_empty">Please enter user name</string>
    <string name="error_password_empty">Please enter password</string>

    <!--Home-->
    <string name="go_to_tours">Go to the Tours</string>
    <string name="shop">Shop</string>
    <string name="jump_to_tour">Jump to Any Tour</string>
    <string name="go_on_tours">Go on tour for free with an expertly-guided virtual-reality pilgrimage to the Holy Land</string>

    <!--Online Tours-->
    <string name="online_tour_more_info">Click here for more information about this tour</string>
    <string name="online_tour_1">In this primer we will begin our 30-tour expedition by taking you to many sites throughout the Holy Land.  On this tour you will quickly discover that the four Gospels describe the geography of this land with incredible accuracy, lending strong credibility to the notion that the original Gospels were authored by men who actually lived here.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_2">In these stories, there were many events recorded in the Gospels that occurred all over the land of Israel, prior to the time of Jesus’ birth, with several stops including Nazareth, the Temple Mount, and Ein Karem (the birthplace of John the Baptist). You will actually go into the Dome of the Rock, and down into the Cave of Souls, under the stone where the Holy of Holies once stood.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_3">This exciting pilgrimage is all about the places and events related to the birth of Jesus. In this excursion you will actually celebrate Christmas Eve in Bethlehem. You will stand in the room where Jesus was born, and you will visit the home where He lived as an infant. You will walk through the caves of the shepherds, and gaze inside their tomb. You will see the graveyard and the bones of the baby boys who died in Bethlehem, and you will spend time in the cave where the Magi hid from King Herod. You will also see the home, most often accepted as the place where Jesus grew up.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_4">On this expedition you will walk through Qumran, you\'ll stand beside the Jordan River, and you will take a cable car up to the Monastery of the Temptation. You will also visit many sites in the country of Jordan that are related to the Gospel, including the place where Jesus was baptized, and the cave home of John the Baptist.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_5">According to The Merged Gospels, Jesus first started gathering disciples in Galilee, and that’s where this tour is located.  The Apostles John and Andrew probably met Jesus on the east side of the Jordan River near Lake Galilee.  Many scholars also believe that John baptized here.  You will walk on the streets of Bethsaida, the hometown of many of Jesus\' Apostles, and you will also visit Cana, where you will see what may be the stone water pots that Jesus used when He turned water into wine. Lastly you will see the church that was built over the traditional home of Nathanael, the Apostle.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_6">This was Jesus first recorded journey to Jerusalem after He began His ministry.  On this tour, you will walk through the Temple Mount, as well as the ruins of Capernaum and Tiberias.  We will also take you to the Gethsemane Grotto, where Jesus probably met with Nicodemus, and then to Ainon near Salim, where John the Baptist was probably arrested.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_7">Our itinerary for this tour will take us through Nablus, where Jesus met the woman at the well, and where you will see what is believed to be a fragment from her skull.  You will visit her home of Sychar (modern Tel Balata).  Then we\'ll go to the top of Mount Gerazim, where 700 Samaritans still live.  You\'ll walk through the location of Jesus\' boyhood synagogue, and you will look over the hill where an angry mob tried to kill Him.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_8">As soon as Jesus appeared in Capernaum, the miracles started to happen. One-fifth of all the stories in The Merged Gospels took place on the streets of Capernaum, and this is where a wealth of Jesus’ teaching occurred. On this exciting tour, will take you all over this ancient city, as well as several other nearby towns that Jesus visited. You will even walk on the path that Jesus took as He traveled from Nazareth to Lake Galilee.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_9">To begin, on this tour you will visit the cave that Jesus prayed in the night before He gave the most famous sermon in the history of the world. Then we will ascend to the top of the ridge, where Jesus selected His Apostles from the disciples who were present. Lastly, you will stand in the very same place that Jesus stood when He delivered the Sermon on the Mount.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_10">On this tour you will take a chartered boat ride on the Sea of Galilee, where you will get a unique 360-degree perspective of the northern shoreline. Through the miracle of immersive video we will take you to Kursi, where Jesus cast the demons into the swine. You will actually go into the caves where the demoniacs used to live - a place that is still the lair of wild boars. There is so much to see, including Nain, where Jesus raised a widow’s son, the Bay of Parables, and the ancient city of Magdala, the hometown of Mary Magdalene.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_11">This tour takes you back to Jerusalem, where you will stand in the Pool of Bethesda, where the ruins are all around you. Here a man had been crippled for 38 years. There’s quite a bit to see, including The Temple Mount, and St. Stephen’s Gate, where it is believed that Stephen was stoned. As an extra treat, we are going to take you down into the Grotto of Jerome, one of the most influential men in all of church history, and explore the secrets of his cave.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_12">On this tour you will stand on the very spot where Jesus probably fed the 5000, and you will walk on the boat dock where He moored near the Gennesaret valley. You will not only walk through the ancient crypt at the Church of St. John the Baptist, but you will enter the ancient tomb where John was buried next to the prophet Elisha. You will enter the Treasure Room at the Church of the Holy Sepulcher, where you will see the skullcap of John, and wood that is believed to be from the cross of Jesus.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_13">This itinerary will take you into some regions less familiar to Israel travelers. We will travel through the Golan Heights to visit Caesarea Philipi, where you actually enter the ancient temple of Pan. You will walk through the streets of Bethsaida, ruins relatively untouched for over 1000 years. You will also ascend Mount Tabor, the traditional site of the Transfiguration. You will walk through Nimrod\'s majestic fortress in the Golan Heights. Lastly you will walk into the Church of the Multiplication, and stand on the site where some believe that Jesus fed the 4000.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_14">One of the most beautiful places on earth is Ein Fawar. This was Jesus’ walking path to Jericho, and it was the site of His Good Samaritan parable. This is one of the places where you can actually stand in Jesus’ three-foot circle. And you will experience the breathtaking sights from the Monastery of St. George, perched high on the cliff of this canyon. Lastly, you will walk through the ruins of Korazim, a city that Jesus cursed. As a side trip, we\'re going to take you back to the Golan Heights to ruins of Tel Dan.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_15">Today you will stand on both the east and west sides of the Mount of Olives. You will walk through the cave where Jesus taught the Lord’s prayer, and where He warned His followers about the end of the world. Other highlights will include a visit through Bethany, the home of Mary, Martha and Lazarus, and to Beit She’an (Israel’s largest archeological site).</string>
    <string name="online_tour_16">This expedition will take you through the original city of Jerusalem, the City of David, where you will see the palace of David, and you will walk through the entire wet tunnel of Hezekiah in the City of David, as well as the dry Canaanite tunnel. You will visit the pool of Siloam, where a man born blind received his sight, and you stand in the synagogue where this man was questioned by Jews.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_17">In this adventure you will visit the Orthodox Church in Bethany, where there is a pedestal, traditionally believed to be the one where Jesus sat as He met with Mary and Martha after the death of Lazarus. You will also go down into the Tomb of Lazarus. Lastly, you will have the very rare privilege of walking through the Hulda tunnels under the Temple Mount, in a place traditionally called Solomon\'s Stables, and today known as the El-Marwani Mosque. As a bonus, we\'re going to take you to the famous city of Megiddo in the Jezreel Valley, the most embattled city in all of Israel.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_18">Most of your time today will be spent exploring the un-restored ruins at the village of Capernaum, Jesus’ ministry home base. Here you will visit the very colorful Church of the 12 Apostles. You will also visit the remote cliffs of Gamla, where thousands of Jews jumped to their death against the advance of the Roman army. We will also take you on a brief visit to the site of the Tower of Siloam, near the City of David. Lastly, as an extra treat, we will show you around two other locations - Mount Carmel, where Elijah fought the priests of Baal, and Hippos, the Roman City overlooking the eastern shore of Galilee - a place that many people believe Jesus visited.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_19">Tour 19 contains many of Jesus’ most important lessons. This pilgrimage follows His walking path down through the middle of Galilee as He made His last journey to Jerusalem. Here our time will be spent mostly in Tiberias, but we will also take you up to the cliffs of Arbel, with its dramatic view of Lake Galilee. You will walk through 17th-century dwellings built by the Druze, as well as caves from which King Herod plucked Hasomean rebels, sending them to their deaths on the crags below. But there are other sites that we will visit - Caesarea by the Sea, a city built by Herod the Great; Masada, the site of the Jew\'s last stand against the Romans, and En Gedi, where David hid from King Saul.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_20">This is rare adventure, because today you will visit Burqin, a town deep in the West Bank, where you will walk into the cave of the 10 Lepers. But there’s more. We have several fascinating side trips for you, such as a trip through Zedekiah’s Cave, and Herod’s spectacular fortress – the Herodium. We will also take you under the Damascus Gate, into Hadrian\'s Forum, built around 135 AD.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_21">Today is more like an expedition than a tour! You are going to go deep into the wilderness to see the Jericho that Jesus knew – ruins that have been untouched since the first century. You will also see Herod’s winter palace, as well as Old Testament Jericho, where Joshua fought his famous battle. You will also enter the monastery built over the traditional home of Zacchaeus, the short man in the tree (See Luke 19:1).</string>
    <string name="online_tour_22">On this journey, we will retrace the steps of Jesus as He walked from Bethany to the place where He acquired the donkey at Bethphage. Then you will head down Palm Sunday Road toward Jerusalem, with a stop at Dominus Flevit, where it is said that Jesus wept over the Holy City. Your Journey will end at the Golden Gate on the eastern wall of the Old City. You will experience all of this in 360° full-spherical video.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_23">Today we will go deep underground into the mysterious Rabbinic tunnels, leading to the spot closest to the ancient Holy of Holies that one can be outside the Temple Mount. On this trip we will also walk through both the Ophel Archeological Park, and the Temple Mount. You will also stand at the famous Western Wall, the holiest site in all of Judaism.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_24">Your travels today will take you through the largest Jewish cemetery in the world, containing over 150 thousand graves. Then we will take you through the dark caverns of the Tomb of the Prophets, where you will actually crawl into the traditional graves of Zechariah, Malachi and Haggai. You will also visit the Pater Noster Convent, where Jesus preached His famous Olivet Discourse, where He predicted the fall of Jerusalem, and the end of the world. We will also take you inside the Russian Orthodox Church of Mary Magdalene, which displays the bones of Mary Magdalene herself.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_25">Today your adventures will take you to Mount Zion, where you will visit the traditional Upper Room, and an alternative to the Upper Room in the Armenian Quarter of the Old City. You will also see the location of the home and final resting place of Mary. You will stand in the traditional home of Caiaphas, and you will walk on the forbidden stairs that Jesus both descended and ascended on the night that He was arrested.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_26">Today we will spend time retracing all of the events that occurred on the night that Jesus was arrested, in the very place where those events took place. This will include touring the Gethsemane Grotto, where Jesus often taught His disciples, the Garden of Gethsemane, and the Church of All Nations with the Rock of Agony where Jesus prayed. We will also follow Jesus’ footsteps through the Kidron Valley as He was escorted by the prison guards. We will also take you to the site of the traditional home of Annas, the High Priest.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_27">On this pilgrimage, you walk down the entire Via Dolorosa, where we will make a stop at each Station of the Cross. You will also walk into the traditional Prison of Christ and Barabbas, the Courtyard of Flagellation, the Lithostratos, and you will see the Judgement Gate through which it is said that Jesus carried the cross. There will be a visit to the Kishle, a new excavation which may contain the pavement on which Jesus was tried by Pilate. You will stand at the altar where the head of the Apostle James is buried, and you will inspect the tombs at Akeldama, the Field of Blood where Judas killed himself. Lastly you will walk through an Ethiopian Monastery on the roof of the Church of the Holy Sepulcher.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_28">Our live tours through the Holy Sepulcher are said to be one of the most complete tours to this sacred shrine, and this 360° tour is no different. We will take you on an exclusive midnight journey through this church, with stops at almost every chapel. And we will escort you through many of the forbidden treasures that very few people ever get a chance to see. But there’s a lot more, including the Garden Tomb, the Monastery of the Cross (the traditional site where the wood from Jesus’ cross was harvested) and the Lutheran Church of the Redeemer.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_29">After Jesus rose from the dead, He was reportedly seen on several occasions, and you will visit all of these sites through The Octagon Project. Several of these sightings took place at the location of The Church of the Holy Sepulcher. Then you will go to the ancient site of Emmaus (probably modern Imwas). Afterward you will once again visit The Upper Room and the Church of St. Mark.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_30">There is much to see on our last days in the Holy Land – the place where Jesus had breakfast with His Apostles, the Mount of Beatitudes, and the place where He ascended into Heaven (The Ascension Chapel). We will also visit some of the sites that came to be during the early church age, such as the Forum of Hadrian directly underneath the Damascus Gate. You will walk around the majestic Monastery of Mar Saba, and we will take you on a tour through Masada – the Jew’s last stand against the Roman army.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_1_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 1–3 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_2_caption">(Available now.  Based on stories 4–8 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_3_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 9–16 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_4_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 17–22 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_5_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 23–25 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_6_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 26–29 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_7_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 30–33 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_8_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 34–52 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_9_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 53–79 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_10_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 80–94 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_11_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 95–97 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_12_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 98–107 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_13_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 108–119 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_14_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 120–134 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_15_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 135–139 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_16_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 140–145 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_17_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 146–150 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_18_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 151–175 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_19_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 176–198 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_20_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 199–202 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_21_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 203–213 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_22_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 214–219 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_23_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 220–233 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_24_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 234–242 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_25_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 243–264 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_26_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 265–270 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_27_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 271–278 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_28_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 279–285 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_29_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 286–295 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_30_caption">(Currently in post–production.  Based on stories 296–299 of The Merged Gospels)</string>

    <!--Signup-->
    <string name="in_order">In order to view a tour you need to do one of the following:</string>
    <string name="login_to_existing">1. Log into your existing account</string>
    <string name="create_account">2. Create an account</string>
    <string name="fname">First Name</string>
    <string name="lname">Last Name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>

    <!--Our Store-->
    <string name="shopping_cart">Shopping Cart</string>
    <string name="checkout">Checkout</string>
    <string name="our_publications">Our Publications</string>
    <string name="merged_gospels_book">The Merged Gospels Book/eBook</string>
    <string name="book_text_short">Scholars are calling The Merged Gospels “a masterpiece”, “powerful and unique”, and “a major work”! This book is the indispensable companion volume, from which you will follow along on all of the Octagon Project video tours.\n\nThe Merged Gospels is not meant to replace the Gospels, and this is why we give you all four Gospels intact and merged.\n</string>
    <string name="book_text_large">The project took 7 years, including 7 trips to Israel, where we literally retraced the steps of Jesus through all 94 geographic sites referred to in the Gospels – a huge undertaking! Unlike typical Gospel harmonies, which only compare blocks of texts between the Gospels, The Merged Gospels breaks all four Gospels down word-by-word. It is first book in history to literally translate the Gospels from the Greek language, merging all of them together into one flowing, chronological narrative, extracting only the duplicated content. Not one word of Scripture has been removed, and all major difference between the Gospels have been highlighted.\n
There are eight benefits to reading The Merged Gospels:\n
1. The Merged Gospels is the companion volume that you will use to follow along with The Octagon Project tours. You will get so much more out of the tour when you are also reading this book.\n
2. It makes the life of Jesus much easier to understand.\n
3. It totally eliminates “so-called” contradictions between the Gospels.\n
4. It takes less time to read The Merged Gospels than it takes to read all four Gospels, because all duplicated content has been removed.\n
5. You will be able to easily compare all four Gospels, because every word and phrase is presented alongside the parallel text from the other Gospels. This will save you a lot of time.\n
6. Every Old Testament verse that is quoted in the Gospels is included next to its New Testament rendering, so you can make comparisons.\n
7. The Merged Gospels is a very literal translation of the Greek text. Smoothing has been sparingly applied for modern readers.\n
8. All throughout we highlight the major Greek variants between the Gospels.</string>

    <string name="merged_gospels_audio">The Merged Gospels Audio Book</string>
    <string name="audio_text_short">Based on The Merged Gospels – Harmonized Edition, this audio book gives you the complete story of Jesus in chronological order. It is a very literal translation of all four Gospels, merged together into a flowing, narrative, but with all of the duplicated content removed.</string>
    <string name="audio_text_large">Read by its author and translator, Dr. Gary Crossland, The Merged Gospels Audio Book gives you a greater understanding of the life of Jesus. By listening to the Gospels in merged format, you will be able to simply and completely follow the footsteps of Christ through every event in His life.
You can order The Merged Gospels Audio Book on either seven CDs or downloadable .mp3 files below.</string>
    <string name="enlarge">Click to enlarge</string>

    <string name="post_production">(Currently in post-production)</string>

    <string name="tour_1_heading">Tour 1 - The Prologue To The Gospel</string>
    <string name="tour_2_heading">Tour 2 - The Years Before Christ</string>
    <string name="tour_3_heading">Tour 3 - The Nativity</string>
    <string name="tour_4_heading">Tour 4 - John The baptist</string>
    <string name="tour_5_heading">Tour 5 - The First Disciples</string>
    <string name="tour_6_heading">Tour 6 - Jesus In Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="tour_7_heading">Tour 7 - The Journey To Nazareth</string>
    <string name="tour_8_heading">Tour 8 - Jesus\' Ministry In Capernaum</string>
    <string name="tour_9_heading">Tour 9 - The Sermon On The Mount</string>
    <string name="tour_10_heading">Tour 10 - Jesus\' Ministry In Galilee</string>
    <string name="tour_11_heading">Tour 11 - The Healings in Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="tour_12_heading">Tour 12 - Adventures in Discipleship</string>
    <string name="tour_13_heading">Tour 13 - Ministry to the Gentiles</string>
    <string name="tour_14_heading">Tour 14 - Lessons on Discipleship</string>
    <string name="tour_15_heading">Tour 15 - The Mount of Olives</string>
    <string name="tour_16_heading">Tour 16 - Jesus\' Confrontation with the Jews</string>
    <string name="tour_17_heading">Tour 17 - Bethany and the city of David</string>
    <string name="tour_18_heading">TOUR 18 - THE CAPERNAUM LESSONS</string>
    <string name="tour_19_heading">Tour 19 - The Final path of Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="tour_20_heading">Tour 20 - The Journey Through Samaria</string>
    <string name="tour_21_heading">Tour 21 - The Jericho That Jesus Knew</string>
    <string name="tour_22_heading">Tour 22 - The Triumphal Ride</string>
    <string name="tour_23_heading">Tour 23 - The Temple Homily</string>
    <string name="tour_24_heading">Tour 24 - The Olivet Discourse</string>
    <string name="tour_25_heading">Tour 25 - The Last Passover</string>
    <string name="tour_26_heading">Tour 26 - Gethsemane</string>
    <string name="tour_27_heading">Tour 27 - The Trials Of Jesus</string>
    <string name="tour_28_heading">Tour 28 - The Death Of Jesus</string>
    <string name="tour_29_heading">Tour 29 - The Glorified Christ</string>
    <string name="tour_30_heading">Tour 30 - The Final Days Of Jesus</string>

    <!--Live Tours-->
    <string name="live_tours_video_heading">Come To The Holyland On A Live Octagon Project Tour</string>
    <string name="live_tours_video_description">An Octagon Tour is the only tour of it’s kind in the Holy Land, because we focus exclusively on the life of Jesus. Every site we take you to is referred to in the Gospels. (Check out our itinerary on this page, and you will see what we mean.) This means that you will be visiting all of the sites that you really came to see.\n\nEvery day we will put you in the three-foot circle of Jesus. You will walk where He walked, sit where He taught, and stand where He did His miracles. All of our guides are Christians, and our itinerary has been designed by Gary Crossland himself. The Merged Gospels is our field guide for our entire trip.\n\nMost of our travelers who have been to Israel before with other tours tell us that ours is about 75% unique. The reason is simple – it’s ALL about Jesus.\n\nThroughout 2016 we have focused our attention on launching The Octagon Project virtual tour. Very soon we will be restarting our Octagon Live Tours to Israel.\n\nAnd what about safety? Don’t be misguided by the media. People are coming to Israel by the droves from all over the world. The fact is that at any moment the safest place to be in the Holy Land is on a tour bus. Since Israel became a sovereign state in 1948 literally no one who has been a part of a tour group has ever been injured or killed there. The reason? Tourists bring money, and everyone wants to sell you something, including the Palestinians. Hence, everyone likes tourists.\n\nPlease get on our mailing list by submitting your contact information here, and we will notify you when we will be taking our next tour to Israel.</string>
    <string name="tour_sites">The Octagon Tour Sites*</string>
    <string name="tour_site_list">Capernaum - the town of Jesus\nThe actual site of the Sermon on the Mount\nThe cave where Jesus prayed all night\nWhere Jesus appointed His Apostles\nThe mountain of the miracle of the swine\nThe site of the feeding of the 5000\nThe site of the great catch of fish\nPeter’s home\nThe Capernaum synagogue\nKorazim, the town that Jesus cursed\nHerod’s palace in Tiberias\nThe home of Mary Magdalene\nA praise boat ride across Galilee\nThe ancient Galilee boat museum\nThe site of the woman at the well\nThe Mountain of Temptation\nHerod’s Jericho palace\nJesus’ baptism site\nThe birthplace of Jesus\nThe infant home of Jesus\nThe shepherds’ field\nThe shepherds’ caves\nThe home of Mary\nThe Nazareth synagogue of Jesus\nAncient Nazareth\nMary’s Spring in Nazareth\nWhen John spent his life in the wilderness\nThe Upper Room\nThe Via Dolorosa\nMount Calvary\nJesus’ Tomb\nThe Western Wall of the Temple\nThe Temple Mount\nThe Pool of Bethesda\nThe Tomb of Lazarus\nThe site of Jesus’ ascension\nThe road where Jesus rode the donkey\nWhere Jesus taught the Lord’s Prayer\nUnder the Church of the Holy Sepulcher\nThe gate through which Jesus carried the cross\nThe roof of the church of the Holy Sepulcher\nThe Pool of Siloam\nThe synagogue, from which the man born blind was cast\nThe palace of Caiaphas\nThe Garden of Gethsemane\nThe Cave of the Ten Lepers\nThe final path of Jesus after Gethsemane\nThe stairs that Jesus ascended before His trial\nThe rock of Christ’s agony in Gethsemane\nJesus’ cave residence at the Mount of Olives\nBethphage, from which Jesus took the donkey\nThe first-century streets of Jerusalem\nThe Old City marketplace\nThe tomb of Joseph of Arimathea\nGabatha, where Jesus was tried by Pilate\nThe Church of St. James the Apostle with his skull\nThe Potter’s Field\nThe Garden Tomb\nSamaria\nThe Mount of Olives\nThe Temple Mount\nThe Tower of Siloam\nGehenna (Hinnom Valley)\nThe site of Jesus post-resurrection fish breakfast at Galilee\n\n*Time restrictions or local conditions may not always permit us to take you to all the sites on this list.</string>

    <!--Comments-->
    <string name="comment_1">We received our copy of the Merged Gospels. Excellent work! Can barely put it down. Love it. Will make a great study resource. Gary and his team did an incredible work that is mind boggling in scope. This will certainly be a great blessing to many today, and will really aid in people’s understanding of the life of the Jesus and of the credibility of the Gospels themselves.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_1">Tammie Pardy</string>

    <string name="comment_2">I have been blessed so much with this book. I purchased it maybe 3 years ago and I have shared this to my friends and other brothers and sisters. I had a burning desire to go back to it and once again let the Word of God wash over me. I thank you so much for your ministry that will affect the generations to come.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_2">Josephine Luzada</string>

    <string name="comment_3">I’m using your book as a leadership study for middle school and high school youth leaders as a means of training them by helping them to learn and implement Jesus’ministry priorities and methods. The plan is that this will translate into how they interact and impact the students that they have intentional relationships with. I’ve done this with a couple of other people (my test group) and it proved to be pretty successful. Thanks for making this resource available…it is being used to impact students here in Colorade for Christ.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_3">Matt Altfeltis</string>

    <string name="comment_4">These books make excellent gifts and everyone I have bought one for has loved it.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_4">Vince Jeevar</string>

    <string name="comment_5">I just viewed Merged Gospels vs. Secularism – what an amazing and much needed teaching. Thank you! I am making plans to show this to our congregation in the near future.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_5">Pastor Harry Hunt</string>

    <string name="comment_6">I am a Lutheran pastor (now “retired”) and I appreciate the scholarly work you have done with The Merged Gospels. I want to say in particular that your translation flows, and I really appreciate the “literal”-ness of it. God bless you.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_6">Marlow Olson</string>

    <string name="comment_7">I love what you’ve done! This Merged Gospels is so much better than a harmony of the Gospels. Merging the narrative makes many of the stories more detailed, more complete, and more meaningful. I was also struck with the sheer number of stories contained in the 4 Gospels. You totally miss that when you read each Gospel individually. Anyway, I love it and can’t stop listening to it! I thank God that you responded to the leading of the Holy Sprit to do this difficult job. God Bless you!</string>
    <string name="comment_author_7">Tom Cray</string>

    <string name="comment_8">I read The Merged Gospels for 90 minutes each morning. It’s a simpler layout to know and read about the life of Jesus. Never I have seen an easier book to understand, rather than jumping between chapters and books in the Bible.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_8">Sam Salsbury</string>

    <string name="comment_9">I’m loving The Merged Gospels!</string>
    <string name="comment_author_9">Dr. Ed Skidmore (Pastor)</string>

    <string name="comment_10">Thank you so much. I have to tell you, your work has been such a blessing. I am in a DLC (Disciplemaking, Learning Community) with a gentleman named Bill Allison, and we have studied through the Merged Gospels. It has been so helpful in my life and disciple-making journey. Right now I am mentoring 8 young adult/college aged students through it. Their eyes are opened further with each meeting. It is just good to see historical, Christ-centered scholarship not aim for the head before the heart. Thanks for honoring God and being HUGE encouragement to me.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_10">Doug Rumbold</string>

    <string name="comment_11">The Merged Gospels have made a big impact on me and the men that I am discipling! They are all wanting to go deeper and share the disciple making way of Jesus with others.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_11">Pastor Jesse Bartz</string>

    <string name="comment_12">I am looking forward to reading The Merged Gospels, and using this tool in personal devotions and ministry. Thank you for your dedication and hard work to complete this undertaking and making it available.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_12">Jerry Burton</string>

    <string name="comment_13">I am a chaplain in the military and I, as well as my soldiers and families, devour all spiritual aids like yours that we can obtain, especially my units that wiil be deploying this year. Materials that both deployed soldiers and spouses can have and read/listen to together are vital. Bless you and your ministry.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_13">Joshua Stine</string>

    <string name="comment_14">What a rewarding project, and through many challenges you brought it to completion. Wow. Thanks for the quality workmanship.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_14">Doug Ford</string>

    <string name="comment_15">It sounds like a wonderful tool and I look forward to listening and studying The Merged Gospels.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_15">Mike Burke</string>

    <string name="comment_16">I want to extend my appreciation for your work with The Merged Gospels. I have been listening and referencing it frequently, and it has been very beneficial and has blessed my life. I can’t thank you enough.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_16">Marilyn Hardy</string>

    <string name="comment_17">I had wondered for a while why I had never seen the 4 Gospel accounts put together as one narrative. Then I heard the radio advertisement for the Merged Gospels. Now I’m excited about reading it for myself and to my children.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_17">Marcus Allred</string>

    <string name="comment_18">Thank-you for your awesome ministry. I will eventually order the CD audio version to listen while I work. I am excited to get this book and read it from start to finish.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_18">Merl Freund</string>

    <string name="comment_19">Thank you for the hard work and dedication. I am using this to help me with my devotional ministry.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_19">Dana Appleby</string>

    <string name="comment_20">Thanks Gary for everything. I Love sharing your work and ministry with those we train and disciple.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_20">Bill Allison</string>

    <string name="comment_21">Our associate pastor is going to lead a bible study using The Merged Gospels in which he is asking about 12 men to join him who will commit not only to the study but to leading 12 more through it each of the next two years with the hope that the life of Jesus can be studied in this format for all the men of the church. His objective is to have us study Christ’s ministry and ask/discuss among ourselves what impact that should have in our lives. The hopeful outcome would be fathers teaching children a biblical world view.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_21">Ron Knapp</string>

    <string name="comment_22">I just finished the first part of the Merged Gospels, and it was the most interesting &amp; engaging Gospel reading ever! I love the chronological order with no duplicates plus the dates, locations, and scriptures. This was the first time ever that I looked forward to reading agood novel. The story of Jesus is colorful, alive, and flowing. Thanks again for all the work you put into this. I recommended it to my Bible study group last Sunday. And I’d love to take a Holy Land tour with your company someday.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_22">Mary Farerra</string>

    <string name="comment_23">The youth pastor that i work with at our church told me about this book, and he is planning on going through it with our Senior High Youth Group this Fall.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_23">Dick Middleton</string>

    <string name="comment_24">We are really enjoying THE MERGED GOSPELS. We read it for Bible every night, and it’s fun that you added the OT references when they quote them.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_24">Mike Kendall</string>

    <string name="comment_25">I’ve already enjoyed reading some of the merged gospels and commend you for a first rate job. It is in fact the most important story in the world.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_25">Reed McNeely</string>

    <string name="comment_26">I just wanted to share my MANY, MANY, MANY THANKS for the trip to Israel. I know I don’t say it enough but you are loved &amp; very much appreciated for all you do, all you’ve done, and all the Good Lord has placed in your heart to do for this world &amp; for me.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_26">Grace Wyman</string>

    <string name="comment_27">I love this book. I appreciate all the time that you put into it.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_27">Addison Gerstein</string>

    <string name="comment_28">The Merged Gospels could indeed be a very helpful resource. It could potentially help clarify difficult passages and allow you to see the same story from numerous perspectives. The Merged Gospels is definitely a great study tool with all of its cross-references and the ability to read the actual verses the Gospels refer to.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_28">Dr. Dean Dixon</string>

    <string name="comment_29">I think the “Merged Gospels” is a very helpful tool for anyone to better understand the gospels in whole. With these Gospels merged, all the information and content in each are very precisely put into one book which makes it way easily to study and to grasp every single detail in all the Gospels in just one reading. This resource can help any theologian when trying to study the Gospels.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_29">Stephen Potter</string>

    <string name="comment_30">The Merged Gospels is any easy way to compare all the Gospels to one another. It may also clarify some things that can be difficult to understand. It can be very helpful to new believers in seeing the full story of Christ from start to finish.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_30">Sami Wyatt</string>

    <string name="comment_31">I’m just starting The Merged Gospels, and loving the flow of His ministry in regards to all 4 Gospels! I also saw your segment on YouTube over the book and it was super powerful! Thanks for following God’s lead to write the book!</string>
    <string name="comment_author_31">Kelly Greenwood</string>

    <string name="comment_32">I love your work. It has helped me a ton. I haven’t seen anything like it. Thanks A million.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_32">David Tamm</string>

    <string name="comment_33">Thanks for all your tremendous hard work putting these resources together. I have been taking my volunteers and students (high school and college) through The Merged Gospels, looking at Jesus’ disciple making process,and we are loving it!!!</string>
    <string name="comment_author_33">Seth Dunham</string>

    <string name="comment_34">Your unique and creative approach to ministry encourages me greatly.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_34">Pastor J. Trent Boyd</string>

    <string name="comment_35">The Merged Gospels work is amazing! I am thrilled! Your work is so fantastic, and I want to spread the word about it.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_35">Judith Lawson</string>

    <string name="comment_36">I wanted to tell you that you have done the church and the body of Christ a great service and favor by putting the Gospels together in this way! God bless you.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_36">Charlie McGee</string>

    <string name="comment_37">I have already listen to over 40 minutes of the audio book, and I love it! Thanks for all your help and may God continue to bless you, and use you for His service.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_37">Dan Cormier</string>

    <string name="comment_38">I’m loving the book by the way! It’s awesome having all four Gospel’s right next to each other compare. I really appreciate all of the notes in the appendix as well, explaining apparent contradictions in more detail.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_38">Eric Shiffer</string>

    <string name="comment_39">All I have to say is: AWESOME!</string>
    <string name="comment_author_39">Russell Andrews</string>

    <string name="comment_40">I very much have enjoyed going through the book this past year and look forward to doing it again this summer. I have never marked up a book as much as yours…...that’s a great complement!!</string>
    <string name="comment_author_40">Rick Burns</string>

    <string name="comment_41">You come to my church Calvary of Salt Lake City a bunch of months ago and I with so many others immediately bought The Merged Gospels. I love it! Thank you. Like you said it would way simplified my understanding of the Gospels and you know what it really did! I do 2 home bible studies once a week -1 prison study once a week and few times a year I teach at the rescue mission of Salt Lake City, and I need to tell you that The Merged Gospels go everywhere with me.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_41">Kenneth Marley</string>

    <string name="comment_42">I love your work on the Merged Gospels. I am starting a study of it myself in a couple of weeks. I have to get my guys to purchase it prior to our first meeting. I love it. I can never read the gospels the same any longer.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_42">Bret</string>

    <!--Reviews-->
    <string name="review_1">“Excellent!” “The Merged Gospels is a new and unusual comparison and merger of the Gospels. Both the translation and the merger are excellent! Those love the Bible will be blessed by studying this fine work.”</string>
    <string name="review_author_1">Dr.Stanley Horton, Th.D., Central Baptist Theological Seminary. (Co-author and translator of The New Testament Study Bible, as well as many other books and commentaries; Distinguished Professor Emeritus of Bible and Theology)</string>

    <string name="review_2">“Exceptional!” “The Merged Gospels is probably the most important presentation of the Gospels in our age. To simplify the study of the Gospels, Dr. Garry Crossland has merged every word, event, and teaching of Jesus into a single story. His translation of all four Gospels is exceptional, and His “merging” goes far beyond the traditional “harmony” of the Gospels approach. Every Believer should have this outstanding tool for their study and research in the hassle of thumbing through all four Gospels for the complete picture of Jesus’life and ministry. It will remain open on your study desk daily.”</string>
    <string name="review_author_2">Dr. Bob Ross, Th.D, International Baptist Christian Theological Seminary. (Author of The Jewishness of Jesus)</string>

    <string name="review_3">“Indispensable!” “The Merged Gospels will be very helpful to in-depth student of the Gospels as well as any other who wish to gain a better understanding of the sequence of events in the four Gospels. The work reflects attention to detail and a love of the Scriptures. Dr. Crossland’s introduction to the book is indispensable to understanding his excellent methodology and careful treatment of the Biblical text. I anticipate using it whenever I am involved in serious Bible study.”</string>
    <string name="review_author_3">Dr.Anthony Palma, Th.D., Concordia Seminary. (Professor Emeritus of New Testament; author of many books, including Galatians and Romans – A Study Guide)</string>

    <string name="review_4">“A major work!” “Dr. Crossland has produced a major work. I can only imagine the effort and time it must have consumed. I particularly appreciate the footnotes section, where I could follow his reasons for doing what he did.”</string>
    <string name="review_author_4">Dr. Olin Storvick, Ph.d, University of Michigan. (Former Chairman, Department of Classical Studies, Concordia college, archaeologist and author)</string>

    <string name="review_5">“Creative!” “I applaud you for your hard work, diligence and creative approach.”</string>
    <string name="review_author_5">Dr. Scott Carroll, Ph.D., Miami university. (Founder of the Scriptorium center for Christian antiquities. One of the world’s foremost scholars on ancient Biblical texts.)</string>

    <string name="review_6">“A masterpiece!” “Dr. Gary Crossland’s The Merged Gospels is a seminal work in Biblical Studies for the New Testament. Someone has finally discovered how to bring the four Gospels together in such a way that senior scholars, as well as novice students of the Bible, can read and fully understand the life of Jesus without having to consult several sources at the same time. The Merged Gospels, by Dr. Gary Crossland, is a masterpiece of page layout and Greek translation! Readers will no longer need to switch between several translations, words studies and synoptic parallels in order to complete a trustworthy study of the four Gospels. This unique and original approach to combining the entire Gospel record into one logical work is destined to become the standard desk reference for all students of the Bible.”</string>
    <string name="review_author_6">Dr.Dennis Frey, Th.D., D.Min.(President, Masters International School of Divinity)</string>

    <string name="review_7">“Beautiful!” “The Merged Gospels should be in every minister’s library, in our colleges and churches, and in the homes of all Bible-loving believers. It brings the narrative style that Jesus preached into clear focus, without losing any of the dynamic of the Gospel message. It is indeed a beautiful volume that I am reading with care and pleasure! The ‘many’ who will study it will be greatly blessed.”</string>
    <string name="review_author_7">Dr. Delmar Guynes, Ed.D., University of North Texas. (Former President, Southwestern Assemblies of God University)</string>

    <string name="review_8">“Highly recommended!” “The Merged Gospels is one of the most indispensable tools in Biblical studies! It is an excellent merger of the four Gospels, giving a chronological and comprehensive reading of the life of Christ. I highly recommend it for all!”</string>
    <string name="review_author_8">Dr. Alvin Low, Ph.D., Th.D., Dallas Theological Seminary. (President, ACTS International; auther of many books, including keys to Unlocking the Bible)</string>

    <string name="review_9">“Powerful and unique!” “Countless hours have been spent compiling The Merged Gospels for studying the Gospels. The chronology and merged harmony of this wonderful tool are combined into a powerful and unique narrative!”</string>
    <string name="review_author_9">Dr. Byron Klaus, D.Min., Fuller Theological Seminary. (Prolific author and President of the Assemblies of God Theological Seminary)</string>

    <!--Shopping Cart-->
    <string name="cart_empty">Your cart is currently empty.</string>

    <!--Tour detail-->
    <string name="if_logged_in">If you are logged in, you can watch the introductory video of each tour. When you purchase this tour, you will be able to watch all the 360° videos on your computer and mobile devices, and in virtual reality with any smartphone or VR headgear.</string>
    <string name="order_your_copy">Order your copy of The Merged Gospels by clicking on the picture above.</string>
    <string name="going_deeper">Going Deeper.</string>
    <string name="click_on_any">Click on any picture below to learn more about the places that you will visit on this tour. These are actual screen grabs of our 360° virtual reality tours.</string>
    <string name="amazing_discoveries_title">Free - Amazing Discoveries!</string>
    <string name="amazing_discoveries_text">Read Gary Crossland\'s free book, Amazing Discoveries of the Octagon Project. Click the book cover below.</string>
    <string name="add_to_cart">Add to Cart</string>
    <string name="tour_2_detail">Watch the free introductory video. Then purchase full the tour. It\'s 2.25 hours long! This tour will be added to the rest of your tours in your \"My Account\" page. You can watch them as many times as you want.</string>
    <string name="proto_text">Protoevangelium Of James</string>
    <string name="dome_text">Dome Of The Rock Inscriptions</string>


    <!--Bottom links-->
    <string name="bottom_online_tours">Our Online 360° Tours</string>
    <string name="bottom_shop">Shop</string>
    <string name="bottom_live_tours">Live Tours to the Holy Land</string>
    <string name="bottom_faq">FAQ and System Requirements</string>
    <string name="bottom_reviews">Merged Gospels Scholarly Reviews</string>
    <string name="bottom_comments">Merged Gospels Customer Comments</string>
    <string name="bottom_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="bottom_bookstore">Local Bookstore Policy</string>
    <string name="bottom_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="bottom_permissions">Filming Permissions</string>
    <string name="bottom_photos">Press Photos</string>
    <string name="bottom_more_videos">More Videos</string>
    <string name="bottom_contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="bottom_message">Click here to send us a message</string>
    <string name="bottom_address">The Octagon Project\nPO Box 691705\nSan Antonio, TX 78269-1705</string>

    <!--Filming permission-->
    <string name="filming_permission_title">Filming Permissions</string>
    <string name="filming_permission_text">The Octagon Project has been filming documentaries in Israel since 2005, and specifically using 360° video cameras since July, 2013.\n\n
In its tour videos The Octagon Project had obtained written permission from every shrine and every archeological site that required such permission on the date of filming. Additionally, we were given verbal permission to film at these same locations on the day of filming by the local attendants at each site.\n\n
All shrines controlled by the Custodia Terrae Sancta (the Franciscans) were filmed prior to February 11th, 2016. Subsequent to this date the Franciscans have officially disallowed any 360° filming of their shrines going forward. This stipulation reads, “7. No permission will be given to film with 360-degree cameras.” Christian Information Center\n\n
The Octagon Project respects the right that the Custodia Terrae Sancta has over all activity at their shrines, and we have agreed to fully comply with this stipulation. Therefore, as of February 11th, 2016, we are no longer doing any 360° filming at shrines exclusively controlled by the Custodia Terrae Sanctae.\n\n
Copies of specific written permissions may be furnished to appropriate parties upon request.\n\n
Legal counsel for The Octagon Project is provided by The Justice Foundation - Texas Justice Foundation</string>

    <!--Privacy Policy-->
    <string name="privacy_policy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text">We will never share your personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of The Octagon Project. We work hard to protect you from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of the information that we hold. For this reason:\n\n
1. We encrypt many of our services using SSL (Secure Socket Layer), offering the strongest online encryption on the market.\n\n
2. We process all of your credit card payments through PayPal, which offers our customers a wide choice of payment options, and a secure payment ecosystem for you to securely transact with us in more than 200 global markets, and in most global currencies.\n\n
3. Our servers are housed at GoDaddy, offering the industry’s strongest protection against viruses, hackers and identity thieves. GoDaddy constantly reviews their information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard you against unauthorized access to your data.\n\n
4. When processed online, your credit card information is never captured by The Octagon Project, and is not known by anyone in our company. Additionally, all of your other personal information is restricted, and accessible to only the highest-level employees, who themselves are under strict contractual confidentiality obligations, and who will be terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.</string>

    <!--Bookstore Policy-->
    <string name="bookstore_policy_title">Bookstore Policies</string>
    <string name="bookstore_policy_text">• For bookstore orders, please call 405-227-8243, or email us at staff@octagonproject.com.\n\n
• Credit cards will be accepted as the method of payment. If you wish us to keep your credit card information on file, we will process your order accordingly.\n\n
• All publications will be sold to bookstores for 50% of their suggested retail price, plus the cost for shipping.\n\n
• All products will be shipped on the same day, or the following business day.\n\n
• Rush orders will be shipped, if you so instruct, by one of the express mail services.\n\n
• If you prefer, we will ship via your account with any major carrier service.\n\n
• Prices are subject to change without notices, and all sales are final.</string>

    <!--About us-->
    <string name="about_us_title">About the Octagon Project</string>
    <string name="about_us_text">Dr. Gary Crossland is a Biblical Greek Professor, as well as an historian, author and documentary producer. For many years, he has been leading tours to the Holy Land, publishing videos about Israel, Jordan and Egypt, and guiding fellow scholars to rare and significant Biblical sites. In his journeys Dr. Crossland has literally retraced every recorded footstep of Jesus Christ, studying each site, and archiving thousands of hours of video footage.\n\n
It seems divinely providential that, from a young age, Gary Crossland would pursue a lifelong career doing what his last name so obviously denotes; that is, taking people to the land of the cross. Dr. Crossland spends about three months out of every year in Israel and Jordan, filming, teaching and leading tours.\n\n
He is also the author of The Merged Gospels – the only book in history to literally translate the four canonized Gospels from the original Greek, breaking them down into four columns, then word-by-word, and reassembling them into a flowing narrative, without removing one word of Scripture. Scholars have called The Merged Gospels “a masterpiece”, “excellent”, “indispensable”, “a major work”, “powerful and unique”, and “highly recommended”.\n\n
In our many travels to Israel, we have to come to realize that for every person who is fortunate enough to visit the Holy Land, there are hundreds of others who want to go, but cannot for various reasons – finances, health, mobility, scheduling, or family conflicts.\n\n
In 2012 we learned about the emerging technology of virtual reality (used mostly by gamers), and its younger sibling, augmented reality, which primarily uses 360° live-action video. Through the convergence of history, Biblical geography and this new immersive video technology The Octagon Project was born in 2013.\n\n
Today, The Octagon Project has grown into a team of highly-skilled video cameramen and technicians, specifically trained in the field of 360° full-spherical ultra-high-definition video production.\n\n
Using The Merged Gospels as a walking guide through the Holy Land, The Octagon Project crew has captured and produced countless hours of breathtaking 360° video in over 200 stunning locations. The entire project is the equivalent of a 30-day, expertly-guided tour to the Holy Land.\n\n
Our extended Octagon Project family includes a number of strategic partners, advisors, technicians and Israeli and Jordanian crew members.\n\n
The Octagon Project is a 501(c)(3) charitable corporation with our main offices in San Antonio, Texas.</string>

    <!--FAQ-->
    <string name="howtouse">HOW TO USE</string>
    <string name="q1">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;What is a 360° virtual reality tour?</string>
    <string name="q2">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;How do I watch a 360° virtual reality tour?</string>
    <string name="ans2">There is a tutorial video on your account page when you sign up for your free membership.</string>
    <string name="q3">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;What device should I use?</string>
    <string name="ans3">The Octagon Project has been optimized for use with nearly every device that can connect to the Internet. For a full list of all compatible devices and known issues (if any) click here - KRPano</string>
    <string name="q4">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;What web browser should I use?</string>
    <string name="ans4">For most devices, you should use Google Chrome. For all Apple iOS users, you should use Safari. For all PC-connected HMD’s we recommend Firefox Nightly or Chromium Webvr Build, depending on what kind of computer and head mount display you are using.</string>
    <string name="q5">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Should I use headphones?</string>
    <string name="ans5">Yes. This will give you the most immersive experience. The Octagon Project is loaded with expertly scripted narration, beautiful music, and live audio from all of our locations.</string>
    <string name="q6">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Device Compatibility.</string>
    <string name="ans6">A1: The Octagon Project was developed using the KRPano virtual tour platform. For a full list of compatible devices, and all known issues with the player, click here - KRPano. For more information about webVR technology, compatibility lists, and upcoming advancements click here -<font color="#F0B97C"> Is Web VR Ready</font>\n
A2: Internet connection speed is important when playing any 360° virtual reality tour. The Octagon Project should work on any connection speed higher than 5mb/s. This is approximately the average speed of a 4G/LTE Internet connection. We recommend a connection of 12mb/s or higher for the best experience. To test your Internet speed click here - <font color="#F0B97C">Test My Speed</font></string>
    <!--PASSWORDS AND SECURITY-->
    <string name="pands">PASSWORDS AND SECURITY</string>
    <string name="pands_Q1">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Is my account information protected?</string>
    <string name="pands_ans1">Yes. The Octagon Project uses the most current and robust security measures. Learn more about these rules here - Internet Privacy</string>

    <string name="pands_q2">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Can I share my account login credentials (username and password) with others? </string>
    <string name="pands_ans2">No. This is not recommended. You could lose access to your own account. First, our system will only allow two devices to access your account simltaneously. Secondly (and this is important), to access your account from a second device, you may have to kill/quit the browser (not just close it) on the device you were using during your previous login. Also, if you are logging in using a unique Octagon Project username and password, you are only allowed to access your account with a total of five different IP addresses within a 30-day period. Lastly, please keep your testimony honorable by not sharing passwords.</string>

    <string name="pands_q3">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Why am I getting a warning that says “Warning: Only two devices are allowed to access an account at any given moment..."? </string>
    <string name="pands_ans3">We only allow two users to access an account at any given moment. Either a third person is currently accessing this account, or the browser that was previously used to access the account was not killed/quit. In order for you to access this account, the browser that was previously used to access it may have to be killed/quit, not just closed.</string>

    <string name="pands_q4">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Why has my account been logged out? </string>
    <string name="pands_ans4">If your account has been inactive for over 20 minutes, it will automatically log you out.</string>


    <!--GENERAL QUESTIONS ABOUT THE OCTAGON PROJECT-->
    <string name="generalques">GENERAL QUESTIONS ABOUT THE OCTAGON PROJECT</string>
    <string name="gen_q1">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Does The Octagon Project have any religious or denominational affiliation?</string>
    <string name="gen_ans1">No. The Octagon Project is an inter-denominational, non-profit organization, and our goal is to teach people everywhere about the truth of Gospel with bias.</string>
    <string name="gen_q2">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;What is The Merged Gospels, and how does it relate to The Octagon Project?</string>
    <string name="gen_ans2">The Merged Gospels is a word-for-word translation of the four canonized Gospels, merged into one composite narratitve. It is the field manual for The Octagon Project, and a perfect companion guide to our 30 tours. To purchase your copy, click here - Octagon Project Shop Page</string>
    <string name="gen_q3">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Does The Octagon Project host live tours?</string>
    <string name="gen_ans3">Yes. For more information about upcoming live tours, click here - Octagon Project Live Tours</string>
    <string name="gen_q4">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Why is The Octagon Project equated to a “full 30 day tour to Israel”?</string>
    <string name="gen_ans4">To physically visit all 220+ locations that The Octagon Project has documented, it would take all day, every day, for approximately one full month.
</string>
    <string name="gen_q5">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Does The Octagon Project have permission to film at these locations?</string>
    <string name="gen_ans5">Yes. Either we have obtained written permission from the administrators of all filmed locations, or we have secured permission by the local site attendant at the time of filming.</string>
    <string name="gen_q6">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Why is my account is locked/inaccessible?</string>
    <string name="gen_ans6">In some cases, this is because either someone else is logged into your account, or the browser (not just the window) used in your last visit was not killed/quit. (This is why you should not share passwords.) In other cases it may be caused by a violation of our usage policy. For all issues regarding account access, please email us: info@octagonproject.com</string>
    <string name="gen_q7">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Why am I seeing a message that reads “You have exceeded your 5 IP limit.”</string>
    <string name="gen_ans7">For Octagon Project username and password accounts, we only allow access through 5 IP addresses within any given 30-day period. But don’t worry. You can always access your account through your Facebook page.</string>


    <!--CURRENT ISSUES WITH OUR 1.0 VERSION-->
    <string name="currentissue">CURRENT ISSUES WITH OUR 1.0 VERSION</string>

    <string name="currentissue_q1">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Coding at the bottom of the screen.</string>
    <string name="currentissue_ans1">Sometimes you may see some coding at the bottom of one of our video tours. Simply close the window, and reopen the tour. In most cases this will correct the issue. We are working on this.</string>

    <string name="currentissue_q2">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Missing resolutions</string>
    <string name="currentissue_ans2">While watching one of our tours, certain resolutions may not appear in the status bar of the video player. Simply close your browsing window, and reopen the tour. In most cases this will correct the issue. We are working on this.</string>


    <string name="currentissue_q3">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Computer head mount displays.</string>
    <string name="currentissue_ans3">Certain PC connected HMDs are not currently compatible with The Octagon Project. We are currently working on this, and should have full capability with The Octagon Project 2.0. For more information about Web VR, click here: Is Web VR Ready</string>

    <string name="currentissue_q4">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Video will not start on mobile devices.</string>
    <string name="currentissue_ans4">With mobile devices, after the screen fades to black, you must tap the screen in order for the video to start. Remember also that with Apple iOS devices, you should use the Safari browser.</string>

    <string name="currentissue_q5">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Video will not start on my computer.</string>
    <string name="currentissue_ans5">Remember that with computers you should watch our videos using Google Chrome.</string>
    <string name="currentissue_q6">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Merging my Facebook account with my Octagon Project account.</string>
    <string name="currentissue_ans6">If you start your membership with your Octagon Project account, logging in through Facebook will allow you to merged your accounts at that time. For users who fail to do this, you may end up with two accounts. We are currently working on a solution to merge two separate accounts.</string>


    <!--Footer-->
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="logout_message">Do you really want to logout?</string>
    <string name="return_shop">Return To Shop</string>
</resources>
