<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Octagon</string>
    <string name="facebook_key">1673357266254895</string>
    <string name="status_bar_title">The Octagon Project</string>
    <string name="status_bar_subtitle">A 30-day Virtual Reality Tour to the Holy Land</string>

    <!--Login Screen-->
    <string name="login_status">The Entire Holy Land in Virtual Reality!</string>
    <string name="login_ways">There are two ways to login.</string>
    <string name="way_facebook">1. Through your Facebook account.</string>
    <string name="way_username">2. Use your registered Octagon Project username and password.</string>
    <string name="text_username">Username (case sensitive)</string>
    <string name="text_password">My Password (case sensitive)</string>
    <string name="remember_me">Remember Me</string>
    <string name="text_forgot">Forgot your username or password?</string>
    <string name="login_with_fb">Login with Facebook</string>
    <string name="login">Log In</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>

    <!--Home-->
    <string name="trailer_1">Trailer #1 \n 2-Minutes Overview</string>
    <string name="trailer_2">Trailer #2 \n 8-Minutes In-Depth</string>
    <string name="travel_all">Travel all over the Holy Land for a tiny fraction of the cost</string>
    <string name="stunning_realism">STUNNING REALISM</string>
    <string name="stunning_realism_text">With The Octagon Project you will feel like you are actually walking through Israel, being totally immersed in all of the sights and sounds of the Holy Land. Our specially-formatted videos play on any computer, any mobile device, and all virtual reality headsets.</string>
    <string name="over_sites">OVER 200 SITES</string>
    <string name="over_sites_text">We will take you to every location in the nation of Israel and Jordan that is named in the Gospels...and more! The Octagon Project is the equivalent of an expertly-guided VIP 30-day tour to the Holy Land. You will walk in places where most tourists don\'t have time to visit, or are never allowed to go.</string>
    <string name="free_subscription">FREE SUBSCRIPTION</string>
    <string name="free_subscription_text">There are 30 tours in The Octagon Project. With your free membership you will able to view a 360-degree intro video of each tour at no cost. Then when you are ready, purchase only the full tours that you want to go on. Just click the Free Signup button below.</string>
    <string name="go_to_tours">Go to the Tours</string>
    <string name="free_signup">Free Signup</string>
    <string name="jump_to_tour">Jump to Any Tour</string>
    <string name="para_2_heading">Crawl, climb, and hike on the world\'s greatest journey!</string>
    <string name="para_2_text">You will visit a number of sites that are absolutely off-limits to tourists. And you will stand in the same places where Jesus Himself stood.</string>
    <string name="para_2_sec_1_heading">AWE INSPIRING</string>
    <string name="para_2_sec_2_heading">RARE &amp; MYSTERIOUS</string>
    <string name="para_2_sec_3_heading">DARK &amp; DANGEROUS</string>
    <string name="para_2_sec_1_text">Get ready to be amazed as you take a 3-hour midnight tour through the Church of the Holy Sepulcher. You will celebrate Christmas Eve in Bethlehem, and you will cross the Sea of Galilee in a privately chartered tour boat. You will walk down the entire Via Dolorosa, where we will literally take you into every Station of the Cross. This is the ultimate pilgrimage to the Holy Land!</string>
    <string name="para_2_sec_2_text">On this incredible journey you will witness things that most tourists will never see – such as the skull cap of John the Baptist, and wood from the “True Cross” of Jesus. We will take you to the hill where Elijah was taken up into Heaven. You will walk through the Dome of the Rock, and into the Cave of the Ten Lepers. And you can actually see the real stones of the original tomb of Jesus!</string>
    <string name="para_2_sec_3_text">Some of this can be a little unsettling – like walking into the tombs of the Gerasene demoniacs, where wild boars still live. You will hike through the desert in 120° heat. The Octagon Project will take you into the cave where the Magi hid from King Herod. We will take you down into tomb of John the Baptist, and you will climb down sheer cliffs in Galilee – all in the safety of 360° virtual reality!</string>
    <string name="shop_at_octagon">Shop at the Octagon Project Store</string>
    <string name="online_360">+  360゜ONLINE TOURS</string>
    <string name="merged_gospels">+  THE MERGED GOSPELS</string>

    <!--Online Tours-->
    <string name="ready_title">Tour #2 is now ready for purchase! Preview this tour here.</string>
    <string name="ready_txt">Unlike an actual "live" tour to the Holy Land, The Octagon Project has the capability of escorting you through the entire land in the chronological order of The Merged Gospels. There are 30 tours in The Octagon Project. In every tour there will be a free introductory video, which you can access by becoming a "lite" subscriber. All of the other videos on each tour require that you purchase that particular tour. When you purchase any tour, you will be able to watch all the 360° videos on your computer and mobile devices, and in virtual reality with any smartphone or VR headgear.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_more_info">Click here for more information about this tour</string>
    <string name="online_tour_1">In this primer we will begin our 30-tour expedition by taking you to many sites throughout the Holy Land.  On this tour you will quickly discover that the four Gospels describe the geography of this land with incredible accuracy, lending strong credibility to the notion that the original Gospels were authored by men who actually lived here.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_2">In these stories, there were many events recorded in the Gospels that occurred all over the land of Israel, prior to the time of Jesus’ birth, with several stops including Nazareth, the Temple Mount, and Ein Karem (the birthplace of John the Baptist). You will actually go into the Dome of the Rock, and down into the Cave of Souls, under the stone where the Holy of Holies once stood.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_3">This exciting pilgrimage is all about the places and events related to the birth of Jesus. In this excursion you will actually celebrate Christmas Eve in Bethlehem. You will stand in the room where Jesus was born, and you will visit the home where He lived as an infant. You will walk through the caves of the shepherds, and gaze inside their tomb. You will see the graveyard and the bones of the baby boys who died in Bethlehem, and you will spend time in the cave where the Magi hid from King Herod. You will also see the home, most often accepted as the place where Jesus grew up.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_4">On this expedition you will walk through Qumran, you\'ll stand beside the Jordan River, and you will take a cable car up to the Monastery of the Temptation. You will also visit many sites in the country of Jordan that are related to the Gospel, including the place where Jesus was baptized, and the cave home of John the Baptist.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_5">According to The Merged Gospels, Jesus first started gathering disciples in Galilee, and that’s where this tour is located.  The Apostles John and Andrew probably met Jesus on the east side of the Jordan River near Lake Galilee.  Many scholars also believe that John baptized here.  You will walk on the streets of Bethsaida, the hometown of many of Jesus\' Apostles, and you will also visit Cana, where you will see what may be the stone water pots that Jesus used when He turned water into wine. Lastly you will see the church that was built over the traditional home of Nathanael, the Apostle.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_6">This was Jesus first recorded journey to Jerusalem after He began His ministry.  On this tour, you will walk through the Temple Mount, as well as the ruins of Capernaum and Tiberias.  We will also take you to the Gethsemane Grotto, where Jesus probably met with Nicodemus, and then to Ainon near Salim, where John the Baptist was probably arrested.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_7">Our itinerary for this tour will take us through Nablus, where Jesus met the woman at the well, and where you will see what is believed to be a fragment from her skull.  You will visit her home of Sychar (modern Tel Balata).  Then we\'ll go to the top of Mount Gerazim, where 700 Samaritans still live.  You\'ll walk through the location of Jesus\' boyhood synagogue, and you will look over the hill where an angry mob tried to kill Him.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_8">As soon as Jesus appeared in Capernaum, the miracles started to happen. One-fifth of all the stories in The Merged Gospels took place on the streets of Capernaum, and this is where a wealth of Jesus’ teaching occurred. On this exciting tour, will take you all over this ancient city, as well as several other nearby towns that Jesus visited. You will even walk on the path that Jesus took as He traveled from Nazareth to Lake Galilee.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_9">To begin, on this tour you will visit the cave that Jesus prayed in the night before He gave the most famous sermon in the history of the world. Then we will ascend to the top of the ridge, where Jesus selected His Apostles from the disciples who were present. Lastly, you will stand in the very same place that Jesus stood when He delivered the Sermon on the Mount.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_10">On this tour you will take a chartered boat ride on the Sea of Galilee, where you will get a unique 360-degree perspective of the northern shoreline. Through the miracle of immersive video we will take you to Kursi, where Jesus cast the demons into the swine. You will actually go into the caves where the demoniacs used to live - a place that is still the lair of wild boars. There is so much to see, including Nain, where Jesus raised a widow’s son, the Bay of Parables, and the ancient city of Magdala, the hometown of Mary Magdalene.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_11">This tour takes you back to Jerusalem, where you will stand in the Pool of Bethesda, where the ruins are all around you. Here a man had been crippled for 38 years. There’s quite a bit to see, including The Temple Mount, and St. Stephen’s Gate, where it is believed that Stephen was stoned. As an extra treat, we are going to take you down into the Grotto of Jerome, one of the most influential men in all of church history, and explore the secrets of his cave.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_12">On this tour you will stand on the very spot where Jesus probably fed the 5000, and you will walk on the boat dock where He moored near the Gennesaret valley. You will not only walk through the ancient crypt at the Church of St. John the Baptist, but you will enter the ancient tomb where John was buried next to the prophet Elisha. You will enter the Treasure Room at the Church of the Holy Sepulcher, where you will see the skullcap of John, and wood that is believed to be from the cross of Jesus.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_13">This itinerary will take you into some regions less familiar to Israel travelers. We will travel through the Golan Heights to visit Caesarea Philipi, where you actually enter the ancient temple of Pan. You will walk through the streets of Bethsaida, ruins relatively untouched for over 1000 years. You will also ascend Mount Tabor, the traditional site of the Transfiguration. You will walk through Nimrod\'s majestic fortress in the Golan Heights. Lastly you will walk into the Church of the Multiplication, and stand on the site where some believe that Jesus fed the 4000.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_14">One of the most beautiful places on earth is Ein Fawar. This was Jesus’ walking path to Jericho, and it was the site of His Good Samaritan parable. This is one of the places where you can actually stand in Jesus’ three-foot circle. And you will experience the breathtaking sights from the Monastery of St. George, perched high on the cliff of this canyon. Lastly, you will walk through the ruins of Korazim, a city that Jesus cursed. As a side trip, we\'re going to take you back to the Golan Heights to ruins of Tel Dan.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_15">Today you will stand on both the east and west sides of the Mount of Olives. You will walk through the cave where Jesus taught the Lord’s prayer, and where He warned His followers about the end of the world. Other highlights will include a visit through Bethany, the home of Mary, Martha and Lazarus, and to Beit She’an (Israel’s largest archeological site).</string>
    <string name="online_tour_16">This expedition will take you through the original city of Jerusalem, the City of David, where you will see the palace of David, and you will walk through the entire wet tunnel of Hezekiah in the City of David, as well as the dry Canaanite tunnel. You will visit the pool of Siloam, where a man born blind received his sight, and you stand in the synagogue where this man was questioned by Jews.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_17">In this adventure you will visit the Orthodox Church in Bethany, where there is a pedestal, traditionally believed to be the one where Jesus sat as He met with Mary and Martha after the death of Lazarus. You will also go down into the Tomb of Lazarus. Lastly, you will have the very rare privilege of walking through the Hulda tunnels under the Temple Mount, in a place traditionally called Solomon\'s Stables, and today known as the El-Marwani Mosque. As a bonus, we\'re going to take you to the famous city of Megiddo in the Jezreel Valley, the most embattled city in all of Israel.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_18">Most of your time today will be spent exploring the un-restored ruins at the village of Capernaum, Jesus’ ministry home base. Here you will visit the very colorful Church of the 12 Apostles. You will also visit the remote cliffs of Gamla, where thousands of Jews jumped to their death against the advance of the Roman army. We will also take you on a brief visit to the site of the Tower of Siloam, near the City of David. Lastly, as an extra treat, we will show you around two other locations - Mount Carmel, where Elijah fought the priests of Baal, and Hippos, the Roman City overlooking the eastern shore of Galilee - a place that many people believe Jesus visited.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_19">Tour 19 contains many of Jesus’ most important lessons. This pilgrimage follows His walking path down through the middle of Galilee as He made His last journey to Jerusalem. Here our time will be spent mostly in Tiberias, but we will also take you up to the cliffs of Arbel, with its dramatic view of Lake Galilee. You will walk through 17th-century dwellings built by the Druze, as well as caves from which King Herod plucked Hasomean rebels, sending them to their deaths on the crags below. But there are other sites that we will visit - Caesarea by the Sea, a city built by Herod the Great; Masada, the site of the Jew\'s last stand against the Romans, and En Gedi, where David hid from King Saul.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_20">This is rare adventure, because today you will visit Burqin, a town deep in the West Bank, where you will walk into the cave of the 10 Lepers. But there’s more. We have several fascinating side trips for you, such as a trip through Zedekiah’s Cave, and Herod’s spectacular fortress – the Herodium. We will also take you under the Damascus Gate, into Hadrian\'s Forum, built around 135 AD.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_21">Today is more like an expedition than a tour! You are going to go deep into the wilderness to see the Jericho that Jesus knew – ruins that have been untouched since the first century. You will also see Herod’s winter palace, as well as Old Testament Jericho, where Joshua fought his famous battle. You will also enter the monastery built over the traditional home of Zacchaeus, the short man in the tree (See Luke 19:1).</string>
    <string name="online_tour_22">On this journey, we will retrace the steps of Jesus as He walked from Bethany to the place where He acquired the donkey at Bethphage. Then you will head down Palm Sunday Road toward Jerusalem, with a stop at Dominus Flevit, where it is said that Jesus wept over the Holy City. Your Journey will end at the Golden Gate on the eastern wall of the Old City. You will experience all of this in 360° full-spherical video.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_23">Today we will go deep underground into the mysterious Rabbinic tunnels, leading to the spot closest to the ancient Holy of Holies that one can be outside the Temple Mount. On this trip we will also walk through both the Ophel Archeological Park, and the Temple Mount. You will also stand at the famous Western Wall, the holiest site in all of Judaism.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_24">Your travels today will take you through the largest Jewish cemetery in the world, containing over 150 thousand graves. Then we will take you through the dark caverns of the Tomb of the Prophets, where you will actually crawl into the traditional graves of Zechariah, Malachi and Haggai. You will also visit the Pater Noster Convent, where Jesus preached His famous Olivet Discourse, where He predicted the fall of Jerusalem, and the end of the world. We will also take you inside the Russian Orthodox Church of Mary Magdalene, which displays the bones of Mary Magdalene herself.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_25">Today your adventures will take you to Mount Zion, where you will visit the traditional Upper Room, and an alternative to the Upper Room in the Armenian Quarter of the Old City. You will also see the location of the home and final resting place of Mary. You will stand in the traditional home of Caiaphas, and you will walk on the forbidden stairs that Jesus both descended and ascended on the night that He was arrested.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_26">Today we will spend time retracing all of the events that occurred on the night that Jesus was arrested, in the very place where those events took place. This will include touring the Gethsemane Grotto, where Jesus often taught His disciples, the Garden of Gethsemane, and the Church of All Nations with the Rock of Agony where Jesus prayed. We will also follow Jesus’ footsteps through the Kidron Valley as He was escorted by the prison guards. We will also take you to the site of the traditional home of Annas, the High Priest.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_27">On this pilgrimage, you walk down the entire Via Dolorosa, where we will make a stop at each Station of the Cross. You will also walk into the traditional Prison of Christ and Barabbas, the Courtyard of Flagellation, the Lithostratos, and you will see the Judgement Gate through which it is said that Jesus carried the cross. There will be a visit to the Kishle, a new excavation which may contain the pavement on which Jesus was tried by Pilate. You will stand at the altar where the head of the Apostle James is buried, and you will inspect the tombs at Akeldama, the Field of Blood where Judas killed himself. Lastly you will walk through an Ethiopian Monastery on the roof of the Church of the Holy Sepulcher.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_28">Our live tours through the Holy Sepulcher are said to be one of the most complete tours to this sacred shrine, and this 360° tour is no different. We will take you on an exclusive midnight journey through this church, with stops at almost every chapel. And we will escort you through many of the forbidden treasures that very few people ever get a chance to see. But there’s a lot more, including the Garden Tomb, the Monastery of the Cross (the traditional site where the wood from Jesus’ cross was harvested) and the Lutheran Church of the Redeemer.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_29">After Jesus rose from the dead, He was reportedly seen on several occasions, and you will visit all of these sites through The Octagon Project. Several of these sightings took place at the location of The Church of the Holy Sepulcher. Then you will go to the ancient site of Emmaus (probably modern Imwas). Afterward you will once again visit The Upper Room and the Church of St. Mark.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_30">There is much to see on our last days in the Holy Land – the place where Jesus had breakfast with His Apostles, the Mount of Beatitudes, and the place where He ascended into Heaven (The Ascension Chapel). We will also visit some of the sites that came to be during the early church age, such as the Forum of Hadrian directly underneath the Damascus Gate. You will walk around the majestic Monastery of Mar Saba, and we will take you on a tour through Masada – the Jew’s last stand against the Roman army.</string>
    <string name="online_tour_1_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 1-3 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_2_caption">(Available now.  Based on stories 4-8 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_3_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 9-16 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_4_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 17-22 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_5_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 23-25 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_6_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 26-29 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_7_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 30-33 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_8_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 34-52 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_9_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 53-79 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_10_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 80-94 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_11_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 95-97 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_12_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 98-107 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_13_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 108-119 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_14_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 120-134 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_15_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 135-139 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_16_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 140-145 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_17_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 146-150 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_18_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 151-175 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_19_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 176-198 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_20_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 199-202 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_21_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 203-213 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_22_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 214-219 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_23_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 220-233 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_24_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 234-242 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_25_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 243-264 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_26_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 265-270 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_27_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 271-278 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_28_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 279-285 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_29_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 286-295 of The Merged Gospels)</string>
    <string name="online_tour_30_caption">(Currently in post-production.  Based on stories 296-299 of The Merged Gospels)</string>

    <!--Signup-->
    <string name="signup_way">There are two ways to get on board.</string>
    <string name="trial">Opening an account will allow you to view all of the introductory videos for each of our 30 tours for free.</string>
    <string name="use_fb">Use your Facebook account</string>
    <string name="choose_username">Choose a username and password.</string>
    <string name="fname">First Name</string>
    <string name="lname">Last Name</string>
    <string name="uname">User Name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>

    <!--Our Store-->
    <string name="shopping_cart">Shopping Cart</string>
    <string name="checkout">Checkout</string>
    <string name="our_publications">Our Publications</string>
    <string name="guided_tours_headline">Our 360° Online Guided Tours</string>
    <string name="guided_tours_text">When you purchase any tour, you will be able to watch all the 360° videos on your computer and mobile devices, and in stereoscopic virtual reality with any smartphone or VR headgear.</string>

    <string name="post_production">(Currently in post-production)</string>
    <string name="click_for_description">Click here for a full description and video about this tour</string>

    <string name="tour_1_heading">Tour 1 - The Prologue To The Gospel</string>
    <string name="tour_1_description">During this primer you will be introduced to many of the sites of Israel, and you will receive a complete overview of the entire 30-day Octagon Project tour.</string>
    <string name="tour_2_heading">Tour 2 - The Years Before Christ</string>
    <string name="tour_2_caption">Available now. Introductory price-$4.99. 13 videos. 2.25 hours</string>
    <string name="tour_2_description">Sites visited – The Church of St. Anne (the birthplace of Mary), The Church of the Annunciation, The Dome of the Rock and Cave of Souls, The Church St. Gabriel (the annunciation site), John the Baptist’s Cave, The Church of John the Baptist in Ein Karem (John’s birthplace), Mary’s Spring (Ein Karem), Mary’s Well (Nazareth) and The Temple Mount.</string>
    <string name="tour_3_heading">Tour 3 - The Nativity</string>
    <string name="tour_3_description">Sites visited – Herod’s Grand Palace, the Jerusalem Model, the Church of St. Joseph, the Kathisma (where Mary rested), the Kishle (ruins of Herod’s palace), the International Mary of Nazareth Center, the Milk Grotto (Jesus’ infant home), the Chapel of the Holy Innocents, the Church of the Nativity, Nazareth Ruins, the Ophel Archeological Park, both the Franciscan and the YMCA Shepherd’s Field, the Monastery of Theodosius (the Magi Cave), the Tower of David Museum and the Church of the Visitation (of Mary to Elizabeth).</string>
    <string name="tour_4_heading">Tour 4 - John The baptist</string>
    <string name="tour_4_description">Sites visited – The Ophel Archeological Park, Elijah’s Hill (with John’s cave), En Gedi, the Church of St. John the Baptist in the Old City, the Church of Madaba (the Madaba map), Naharayim (baptism site), Qasr Al Yehud (baptism site), Qumran (the Dead Sea Scrolls), The Monastery of Temptation and Wadi Kharrar (John’s original baptism site in Jordan).</string>
    <string name="tour_5_heading">Tour 5 - The First Disciples</string>
    <string name="tour_5_description">Sites visited – Bethsaida (original home of the first apostles), The Franciscan and Orthodox churches of Cana, Khirbet Kana (ruins of Cana) and Yardenit (baptism site).</string>
    <string name="tour_6_heading">Tour 6 - Jesus In Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="tour_6_description">Sites visited – Capernaum, the Gethsemane Grotto, Ainon near Salim (where John baptized, Tiberias, The Temple Mount and the Jerusalem Model.</string>
    <string name="tour_7_heading">Tour 7 - The Journey To Nazareth</string>
    <string name="tour_7_description">Sites visited – Sychar (where Jesus stayed 3 days), Mount Gerazim (where the Samaritans still worship), Magdala (home of Mary Magdalene), the Maronite Cliff (where a crowd tried to kill Jesus), Megiddo, the Church of Saint Photini (the woman at the well), Mount Precipice and the Synagogue Church (Jesus’ childhood synagogue).</string>
    <string name="tour_8_heading">Tour 8 - Jesus\' Ministry In Capernaum</string>
    <string name="tour_8_description">Sites visited – Capernaum, Peter’s home, the Capernaum synagogue, the Sea of Galilee, Gamla (where thousands of Jews ended their own lives, Hippos, Korazin (the town Jesus cursed) and the Valley of the Doves (the path of Jesus from Nazareth to Capernaum).</string>
    <string name="tour_9_heading">Tour 9 - The Sermon On The Mount</string>
    <string name="tour_9_description">Sites visited – The traditional Church of the Beatitudes, the actual site of the Sermon on the Mount, the Eremos Cave (where Jesus prayed) and the Eremos Heights (where Jesus appointed His 12 Apostles).</string>
    <string name="tour_10_heading">Tour 10 - Jesus\' Ministry In Galilee</string>
    <string name="tour_10_description">Sites visited – A boat ride on the Sea of Galilee, Kursi (where Jesus cast the demons into the swine), Nain (where Jesus raised a widow’s son), the Bay of Parables, the Church of the 12 Apostles, Capernaum, the Temple Mount and Tiberias.</string>
    <string name="tour_11_heading">Tour 11 - The Healings in Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="tour_11_description">Sites visited – The Pool of Bethesda, Hezekiah’s Broad Wall, the St. Stephen’s Gate, Capernaum and the Jerusalem Model.</string>
    <string name="tour_12_heading">Tour 12 - Adventures in Discipleship</string>
    <string name="tour_12_description">Sites visited – Sebastia (Samaria), the cliffs of Arbel (overlooking the Sea of Galilee), an ancient Genessaret boat dock, Har Menorim (the Feeding of the 5000), the Church of John the Baptist in Sebastia, the tomb of John the Baptist, Capernaum, Tiberias, Galilee and Bethsaida.</string>
    <string name="tour_13_heading">Tour 13 - Ministry to the Gentiles</string>
    <string name="tour_13_description">Sites visited – Caesarea Philipi, the Church of the Multiplication, Nimrod’s Fortress, Mount Tabor (the traditional site of the Transfiguration of Jesus), Tel Dan, Tel Hadar (possible site of the feeding of the 4000), Capernaum, Bethsaida and Magdala.</string>
    <string name="tour_14_heading">Tour 14 - Lessons on Discipleship</string>
    <string name="tour_14_description">Sites visited – Ein Fawar (Jesus’ walking path to Jericho), the Monastery of St. George in Wadi Qelt, Capernaum, Sebastia and the Temple Mount.</string>
    <string name="tour_15_heading">Tour 15 - The Mount of Olives</string>
    <string name="tour_15_description">Sites visited – Beit She’an (Israel’s largest archeological site), the Bethany crusader ruins, the Bethany Church of St. Lazarus, the Pater Noster Convent (where Jesus taught The Lord’s Prayer, and the Temple Mount.</string>
    <string name="tour_16_heading">Tour 16 - Jesus\' Confrontation with the Jews</string>
    <string name="tour_16_description">Sites visited – The Bethany Orthodox Church (with the Seat of Jesus, the Canaanite Tunnel, Hezekiah’s drainage tunnel, Lazarus’ Tomb, the Temple Mount and the Jerusalem Model.</string>
    <string name="tour_17_heading">Tour 17 - Bethany and the city of David</string>
    <string name="tour_17_description">Sites visited – The City of David, the covered Herodian street, David’s palace, the Pool of Siloam, the Theodotus Synagogue (the story of the Man born blind), the Tower of Siloam, Wadi Kharrar, the Temple Mount and Capernaum.</string>
    <string name="tour_18_heading">TOUR 18 - THE CAPERNAUM LESSONS</string>
    <string name="tour_18_description">Coming soon</string>
    <string name="tour_19_heading">Tour 19 - The Final path of Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="tour_19_description">Sites visited – Tiberias, the palace of Herod Antipas and the Temple Mount.</string>
    <string name="tour_20_heading">Tour 20 - The Journey Through Samaria</string>
    <string name="tour_20_description">Sites visited – Burquin (the cave of the 10 Lepers), Zedekiah’s Cave, Mount Carmel, the Herodion, Herod’s Gate, the Jaffa Gate, the Dung Gate, the New Gate and Stella Maris (the cave of Elijah).</string>
    <string name="tour_21_heading">Tour 21 - The Jericho That Jesus Knew</string>
    <string name="tour_21_description">Sites visited – The Judean Wilderness, both Herodian and Old Testament Jericho, they Sycamore Tree in Jericho, and Wadi Kharrar (the original baptism site of John).</string>
    <string name="tour_22_heading">Tour 22 - The Triumphal Ride</string>
    <string name="tour_22_description">Sites visited – Bethphage (where Jesus borrowed the donkey), Dominus Flevit (where Jesus wept), Palm Sunday Road from Bethany to Jerusalem, the Golden Gate on the eastern wall of the Temple Mount, the Temple Mount, the Jerusalem Model, and various sites in Bethany.</string>
    <string name="tour_23_heading">Tour 23 - The Temple Homily</string>
    <string name="tour_23_description">Sites visited – The Rabbinic tunnels under Jerusalem, the Western Wall and Wilson Arch Library, the Ophel Archeological Park, the Temple Mount, and the Jerusalem model.</string>
    <string name="tour_24_heading">Tour 24 - The Olivet Discourse</string>
    <string name="tour_24_description">Sites visited – The Cemetery on the Mount of Olives, the Tomb of the Prophets, and the Pater Noster Convent.</string>
    <string name="tour_25_heading">Tour 25 - The Last Passover</string>
    <string name="tour_25_description">Sites visited – David’s Tomb, the Dormition Abbey (where Mary died), St. Peter in Gallicantu (the traditional home of Caiaphas), the Maccabean Stairs (where Jesus walked), the Upper Room (Cenacle), the Church of St. Mark (the alternative Upper Room), the Zion Gate and Oscar Schindlar’s grave.</string>
    <string name="tour_26_heading">Tour 26 - Gethsemane</string>
    <string name="tour_26_description">Sites visited – The Garden of Gethsemane, the traditional home of the high priest Annas, the Church of All Nations (with the Stone of Agony), the Kidron Valley and tombs, Mary’s Tomb, the Gethsemane Grotto, and the Church of St. Peter in Gallicantu.</string>
    <string name="tour_27_heading">Tour 27 - The Trials Of Jesus</string>
    <string name="tour_27_description">Sites visited – The Via Dolorosa (with all the Stations of the Cross), the Prison of Christ and Barabbas, the Lithostratos, the Church of St. James, the location of the Hasmonean Palace (Jesus’ trial with Herod), Gabbatha, the Kishle (ruins of Herod’s palace), the Courtyard of Flagellation, the Alexander Nevsky Compound (with the Judgment Gate), the Potter’s Field, the Temple Mount and the Jerusalem Model.</string>
    <string name="tour_28_heading">Tour 28 - The Death Of Jesus</string>
    <string name="tour_28_description">Sites visited – The Church of the Holy Sepulcher (including all chapels), the Garden Tomb, the Monastery of the Cross (from where the cross was cut), the Lutheran Church of the Redeemer, the Byzantine Model, the Jerusalem Model, and Herod Agrippa’s Third Wall.</string>
    <string name="tour_29_heading">Tour 29 - The Glorified Christ</string>
    <string name="tour_29_description">Sites visited – Emmaus, the Church of Mary Magdalene, the Church of the Holy Sepulcher, the Mensa Christi Chapel in Nazareth, the Church of St. Mark, the Upper Room (Cenacle) and the Temple Mount.</string>
    <string name="tour_30_heading">Tour 30 - The Final Days Of Jesus</string>
    <string name="tour_30_description">Sites visited – The Ascension Chapel, the Damascus Gate, the Cardo Maximus, Hadrian’s Forum, the Monastery of Mar Saba, Masada, the Church of Peter’s Primacy, the site of the Sermon on the Mount, the Ophel Archeological Park, and the Zion Gate.</string>

    <!--Live Tours-->
    <string name="live_tours_video_heading">Come To The Holyland On A Live Octagon Project Tour</string>
    <string name="live_tours_video_description">An Octagon Tour is the only tour of it’s kind in the Holy Land, because we focus exclusively on the life of Jesus. Every site we take you to is referred to in the Gospels. (Check out our itinerary on this page, and you will see what we mean.) This means that you will be visiting all of the sites that you really came to see.\n\nEvery day we will put you in the three-foot circle of Jesus. You will walk where He walked, sit where He taught, and stand where He did His miracles. All of our guides are Christians, and our itinerary has been designed by Gary Crossland himself. The Merged Gospels is our field guide for our entire trip.\n\nMost of our travelers who have been to Israel before with other tours tell us that ours is about 75% unique. The reason is simple – it’s ALL about Jesus.\n\nThroughout 2016 we have focused our attention on launching The Octagon Project virtual tour. Very soon we will be restarting our Octagon Live Tours to Israel.\n\nAnd what about safety? Don’t be misguided by the media. People are coming to Israel by the droves from all over the world. The fact is that at any moment the safest place to be in the Holy Land is on a tour bus. Since Israel became a sovereign state in 1948 literally no one who has been a part of a tour group has ever been injured or killed there. The reason? Tourists bring money, and everyone wants to sell you something, including the Palestinians. Hence, everyone likes tourists.\n\nPlease get on our mailing list by submitting your contact information here, and we will notify you when we will be taking our next tour to Israel.</string>
    <string name="tour_sites">The Octagon Tour Sites*</string>
    <string name="tour_site_list">Capernaum - the town of Jesus\nThe actual site of the Sermon on the Mount\nThe cave where Jesus prayed all night\nWhere Jesus appointed His Apostles\nThe mountain of the miracle of the swine\nThe site of the feeding of the 5000\nThe site of the great catch of fish\nPeter’s home\nThe Capernaum synagogue\nKorazim, the town that Jesus cursed\nHerod’s palace in Tiberias\nThe home of Mary Magdalene\nA praise boat ride across Galilee\nThe ancient Galilee boat museum\nThe site of the woman at the well\nThe Mountain of Temptation\nHerod’s Jericho palace\nJesus’ baptism site\nThe birthplace of Jesus\nThe infant home of Jesus\nThe shepherds’ field\nThe shepherds’ caves\nThe home of Mary\nThe Nazareth synagogue of Jesus\nAncient Nazareth\nMary’s Spring in Nazareth\nWhen John spent his life in the wilderness\nThe Upper Room\nThe Via Dolorosa\nMount Calvary\nJesus’ Tomb\nThe Western Wall of the Temple\nThe Temple Mount\nThe Pool of Bethesda\nThe Tomb of Lazarus\nThe site of Jesus’ ascension\nThe road where Jesus rode the donkey\nWhere Jesus taught the Lord’s Prayer\nUnder the Church of the Holy Sepulcher\nThe gate through which Jesus carried the cross\nThe roof of the church of the Holy Sepulcher\nThe Pool of Siloam\nThe synagogue, from which the man born blind was cast\nThe palace of Caiaphas\nThe Garden of Gethsemane\nThe Cave of the Ten Lepers\nThe final path of Jesus after Gethsemane\nThe stairs that Jesus ascended before His trial\nThe rock of Christ’s agony in Gethsemane\nJesus’ cave residence at the Mount of Olives\nBethphage, from which Jesus took the donkey\nThe first-century streets of Jerusalem\nThe Old City marketplace\nThe tomb of Joseph of Arimathea\nGabatha, where Jesus was tried by Pilate\nThe Church of St. James the Apostle with his skull\nThe Potter’s Field\nThe Garden Tomb\nSamaria\nThe Mount of Olives\nThe Temple Mount\nThe Tower of Siloam\nGehenna (Hinnom Valley)\nThe site of Jesus post-resurrection fish breakfast at Galilee\n\n*Time restrictions or local conditions may not always permit us to take you to all the sites on this list.</string>
    
    <!--Comments-->
    <string name="comment_1">We received our copy of the Merged Gospels. Excellent work! Can barely put it down. Love it. Will make a great study resource. Gary and his team did an incredible work that is mind boggling in scope. This will certainly be a great blessing to many today, and will really aid in people’s understanding of the life of the Jesus and of the credibility of the Gospels themselves.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_1">Tammie Pardy</string>

    <string name="comment_2">I have been blessed so much with this book. I purchased it maybe 3 years ago and I have shared this to my friends and other brothers and sisters. I had a burning desire to go back to it and once again let the Word of God wash over me. I thank you so much for your ministry that will affect the generations to come.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_2">Josephine Luzada</string>

    <string name="comment_3">I’m using your book as a leadership study for middle school and high school youth leaders as a means of training them by helping them to learn and implement Jesus’ministry priorities and methods. The plan is that this will translate into how they interact and impact the students that they have intentional relationships with. I’ve done this with a couple of other people (my test group) and it proved to be pretty successful. Thanks for making this resource available…it is being used to impact students here in Colorade for Christ.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_3">Matt Altfeltis</string>

    <string name="comment_4">These books make excellent gifts and everyone I have bought one for has loved it.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_4">Vince Jeevar</string>

    <string name="comment_5">I just viewed Merged Gospels vs. Secularism – what an amazing and much needed teaching. Thank you! I am making plans to show this to our congregation in the near future.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_5">Pastor Harry Hunt</string>

    <string name="comment_6">I am a Lutheran pastor (now “retired”) and I appreciate the scholarly work you have done with The Merged Gospels. I want to say in particular that your translation flows, and I really appreciate the “literal”-ness of it. God bless you.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_6">Marlow Olson</string>

    <string name="comment_7">I love what you’ve done! This Merged Gospels is so much better than a harmony of the Gospels. Merging the narrative makes many of the stories more detailed, more complete, and more meaningful. I was also struck with the sheer number of stories contained in the 4 Gospels. You totally miss that when you read each Gospel individually. Anyway, I love it and can’t stop listening to it! I thank God that you responded to the leading of the Holy Sprit to do this difficult job. God Bless you!</string>
    <string name="comment_author_7">Tom Cray</string>

    <string name="comment_8">I read The Merged Gospels for 90 minutes each morning. It’s a simpler layout to know and read about the life of Jesus. Never I have seen an easier book to understand, rather than jumping between chapters and books in the Bible.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_8">Sam Salsbury</string>

    <string name="comment_9">I’m loving The Merged Gospels!</string>
    <string name="comment_author_9">Dr. Ed Skidmore (Pastor)</string>

    <string name="comment_10">Thank you so much. I have to tell you, your work has been such a blessing. I am in a DLC (Disciplemaking, Learning Community) with a gentleman named Bill Allison, and we have studied through the Merged Gospels. It has been so helpful in my life and disciple-making journey. Right now I am mentoring 8 young adult/college aged students through it. Their eyes are opened further with each meeting. It is just good to see historical, Christ-centered scholarship not aim for the head before the heart. Thanks for honoring God and being HUGE encouragement to me.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_10">Doug Rumbold</string>

    <string name="comment_11">The Merged Gospels have made a big impact on me and the men that I am discipling! They are all wanting to go deeper and share the disciple making way of Jesus with others.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_11">Pastor Jesse Bartz</string>

    <string name="comment_12">I am looking forward to reading The Merged Gospels, and using this tool in personal devotions and ministry. Thank you for your dedication and hard work to complete this undertaking and making it available.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_12">Jerry Burton</string>

    <string name="comment_13">I am a chaplain in the military and I, as well as my soldiers and families, devour all spiritual aids like yours that we can obtain, especially my units that wiil be deploying this year. Materials that both deployed soldiers and spouses can have and read/listen to together are vital. Bless you and your ministry.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_13">Joshua Stine</string>

    <string name="comment_14">What a rewarding project, and through many challenges you brought it to completion. Wow. Thanks for the quality workmanship.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_14">Doug Ford</string>

    <string name="comment_15">It sounds like a wonderful tool and I look forward to listening and studying The Merged Gospels.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_15">Mike Burke</string>

    <string name="comment_16">I want to extend my appreciation for your work with The Merged Gospels. I have been listening and referencing it frequently, and it has been very beneficial and has blessed my life. I can’t thank you enough.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_16">Marilyn Hardy</string>

    <string name="comment_17">I had wondered for a while why I had never seen the 4 Gospel accounts put together as one narrative. Then I heard the radio advertisement for the Merged Gospels. Now I’m excited about reading it for myself and to my children.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_17">Marcus Allred</string>

    <string name="comment_18">Thank-you for your awesome ministry. I will eventually order the CD audio version to listen while I work. I am excited to get this book and read it from start to finish.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_18">Merl Freund</string>

    <string name="comment_19">Thank you for the hard work and dedication. I am using this to help me with my devotional ministry.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_19">Dana Appleby</string>

    <string name="comment_20">Thanks Gary for everything. I Love sharing your work and ministry with those we train and disciple.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_20">Bill Allison</string>

    <string name="comment_21">Our associate pastor is going to lead a bible study using The Merged Gospels in which he is asking about 12 men to join him who will commit not only to the study but to leading 12 more through it each of the next two years with the hope that the life of Jesus can be studied in this format for all the men of the church. His objective is to have us study Christ’s ministry and ask/discuss among ourselves what impact that should have in our lives. The hopeful outcome would be fathers teaching children a biblical world view.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_21">Ron Knapp</string>

    <string name="comment_22">I just finished the first part of the Merged Gospels, and it was the most interesting &amp; engaging Gospel reading ever! I love the chronological order with no duplicates plus the dates, locations, and scriptures. This was the first time ever that I looked forward to reading agood novel. The story of Jesus is colorful, alive, and flowing. Thanks again for all the work you put into this. I recommended it to my Bible study group last Sunday. And I’d love to take a Holy Land tour with your company someday.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_22">Mary Farerra</string>

    <string name="comment_23">The youth pastor that i work with at our church told me about this book, and he is planning on going through it with our Senior High Youth Group this Fall.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_23">Dick Middleton</string>

    <string name="comment_24">We are really enjoying THE MERGED GOSPELS. We read it for Bible every night, and it’s fun that you added the OT references when they quote them.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_24">Mike Kendall</string>

    <string name="comment_25">I’ve already enjoyed reading some of the merged gospels and commend you for a first rate job. It is in fact the most important story in the world.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_25">Reed McNeely</string>

    <string name="comment_26">I just wanted to share my MANY, MANY, MANY THANKS for the trip to Israel. I know I don’t say it enough but you are loved &amp; very much appreciated for all you do, all you’ve done, and all the Good Lord has placed in your heart to do for this world &amp; for me.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_26">Grace Wyman</string>

    <string name="comment_27">I love this book. I appreciate all the time that you put into it.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_27">Addison Gerstein</string>

    <string name="comment_28">The Merged Gospels could indeed be a very helpful resource. It could potentially help clarify difficult passages and allow you to see the same story from numerous perspectives. The Merged Gospels is definitely a great study tool with all of its cross-references and the ability to read the actual verses the Gospels refer to.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_28">Dr. Dean Dixon</string>

    <string name="comment_29">I think the “Merged Gospels” is a very helpful tool for anyone to better understand the gospels in whole. With these Gospels merged, all the information and content in each are very precisely put into one book which makes it way easily to study and to grasp every single detail in all the Gospels in just one reading. This resource can help any theologian when trying to study the Gospels.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_29">Stephen Potter</string>

    <string name="comment_30">The Merged Gospels is any easy way to compare all the Gospels to one another. It may also clarify some things that can be difficult to understand. It can be very helpful to new believers in seeing the full story of Christ from start to finish.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_30">Sami Wyatt</string>

    <string name="comment_31">I’m just starting The Merged Gospels, and loving the flow of His ministry in regards to all 4 Gospels! I also saw your segment on YouTube over the book and it was super powerful! Thanks for following God’s lead to write the book!</string>
    <string name="comment_author_31">Kelly Greenwood</string>

    <string name="comment_32">I love your work. It has helped me a ton. I haven’t seen anything like it. Thanks A million.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_32">David Tamm</string>

    <string name="comment_33">Thanks for all your tremendous hard work putting these resources together. I have been taking my volunteers and students (high school and college) through The Merged Gospels, looking at Jesus’ disciple making process,and we are loving it!!!</string>
    <string name="comment_author_33">Seth Dunham</string>

    <string name="comment_34">Your unique and creative approach to ministry encourages me greatly.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_34">Pastor J. Trent Boyd</string>

    <string name="comment_35">The Merged Gospels work is amazing! I am thrilled! Your work is so fantastic, and I want to spread the word about it.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_35">Judith Lawson</string>

    <string name="comment_36">I wanted to tell you that you have done the church and the body of Christ a great service and favor by putting the Gospels together in this way! God bless you.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_36">Charlie McGee</string>

    <string name="comment_37">I have already listen to over 40 minutes of the audio book, and I love it! Thanks for all your help and may God continue to bless you, and use you for His service.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_37">Dan Cormier</string>

    <string name="comment_38">I’m loving the book by the way! It’s awesome having all four Gospel’s right next to each other compare. I really appreciate all of the notes in the appendix as well, explaining apparent contradictions in more detail.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_38">Eric Shiffer</string>

    <string name="comment_39">All I have to say is: AWESOME!</string>
    <string name="comment_author_39">Russell Andrews</string>

    <string name="comment_40">I very much have enjoyed going through the book this past year and look forward to doing it again this summer. I have never marked up a book as much as yours…...that’s a great complement!!</string>
    <string name="comment_author_40">Rick Burns</string>

    <string name="comment_41">You come to my church Calvary of Salt Lake City a bunch of months ago and I with so many others immediately bought The Merged Gospels. I love it! Thank you. Like you said it would way simplified my understanding of the Gospels and you know what it really did! I do 2 home bible studies once a week -1 prison study once a week and few times a year I teach at the rescue mission of Salt Lake City, and I need to tell you that The Merged Gospels go everywhere with me.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_41">Kenneth Marley</string>

    <string name="comment_42">I love your work on the Merged Gospels. I am starting a study of it myself in a couple of weeks. I have to get my guys to purchase it prior to our first meeting. I love it. I can never read the gospels the same any longer.</string>
    <string name="comment_author_42">Bret</string>

    <!--Reviews-->
    <string name="review_1">“Excellent!” “The Merged Gospels is a new and unusual comparison and merger of the Gospels. Both the translation and the merger are excellent! Those love the Bible will be blessed by studying this fine work.”</string>
    <string name="review_author_1">Dr.Stanley Horton, Th.D., Central Baptist Theological Seminary. (Co-author and translator of The New Testament Study Bible, as well as many other books and commentaries; Distinguished Professor Emeritus of Bible and Theology)</string>

    <string name="review_2">“Exceptional!” “The Merged Gospels is probably the most important presentation of the Gospels in our age. To simplify the study of the Gospels, Dr. Garry Crossland has merged every word, event, and teaching of Jesus into a single story. His translation of all four Gospels is exceptional, and His “merging” goes far beyond the traditional “harmony” of the Gospels approach. Every Believer should have this outstanding tool for their study and research in the hassle of thumbing through all four Gospels for the complete picture of Jesus’life and ministry. It will remain open on your study desk daily.”</string>
    <string name="review_author_2">Dr. Bob Ross, Th.D, International Baptist Christian Theological Seminary. (Author of The Jewishness of Jesus)</string>

    <string name="review_3">“Indispensable!” “The Merged Gospels will be very helpful to in-depth student of the Gospels as well as any other who wish to gain a better understanding of the sequence of events in the four Gospels. The work reflects attention to detail and a love of the Scriptures. Dr. Crossland’s introduction to the book is indispensable to understanding his excellent methodology and careful treatment of the Biblical text. I anticipate using it whenever I am involved in serious Bible study.”</string>
    <string name="review_author_3">Dr.Anthony Palma, Th.D., Concordia Seminary. (Professor Emeritus of New Testament; author of many books, including Galatians and Romans – A Study Guide)</string>

    <string name="review_4">“A major work!” “Dr. Crossland has produced a major work. I can only imagine the effort and time it must have consumed. I particularly appreciate the footnotes section, where I could follow his reasons for doing what he did.”</string>
    <string name="review_author_4">Dr. Olin Storvick, Ph.d, University of Michigan. (Former Chairman, Department of Classical Studies, Concordia college, archaeologist and author)</string>

    <string name="review_5">“Creative!” “I applaud you for your hard work, diligence and creative approach.”</string>
    <string name="review_author_5">Dr. Scott Carroll, Ph.D., Miami university. (Founder of the Scriptorium center for Christian antiquities. One of the world’s foremost scholars on ancient Biblical texts.)</string>

    <string name="review_6">“A masterpiece!” “Dr. Gary Crossland’s The Merged Gospels is a seminal work in Biblical Studies for the New Testament. Someone has finally discovered how to bring the four Gospels together in such a way that senior scholars, as well as novice students of the Bible, can read and fully understand the life of Jesus without having to consult several sources at the same time. The Merged Gospels, by Dr. Gary Crossland, is a masterpiece of page layout and Greek translation! Readers will no longer need to switch between several translations, words studies and synoptic parallels in order to complete a trustworthy study of the four Gospels. This unique and original approach to combining the entire Gospel record into one logical work is destined to become the standard desk reference for all students of the Bible.”</string>
    <string name="review_author_6">Dr.Dennis Frey, Th.D., D.Min.(President, Masters International School of Divinity)</string>

    <string name="review_7">“Beautiful!” “The Merged Gospels should be in every minister’s library, in our colleges and churches, and in the homes of all Bible-loving believers. It brings the narrative style that Jesus preached into clear focus, without losing any of the dynamic of the Gospel message. It is indeed a beautiful volume that I am reading with care and pleasure! The ‘many’ who will study it will be greatly blessed.”</string>
    <string name="review_author_7">Dr. Delmar Guynes, Ed.D., University of North Texas. (Former President, Southwestern Assemblies of God University)</string>

    <string name="review_8">“Highly recommended!” “The Merged Gospels is one of the most indispensable tools in Biblical studies! It is an excellent merger of the four Gospels, giving a chronological and comprehensive reading of the life of Christ. I highly recommend it for all!”</string>
    <string name="review_author_8">Dr. Alvin Low, Ph.D., Th.D., Dallas Theological Seminary. (President, ACTS International; auther of many books, including keys to Unlocking the Bible)</string>

    <string name="review_9">“Powerful and unique!” “Countless hours have been spent compiling The Merged Gospels for studying the Gospels. The chronology and merged harmony of this wonderful tool are combined into a powerful and unique narrative!”</string>
    <string name="review_author_9">Dr. Byron Klaus, D.Min., Fuller Theological Seminary. (Prolific author and President of the Assemblies of God Theological Seminary)</string>

    <!--Shopping Cart-->
    <string name="cart_empty">Your cart is currently empty.</string>
</resources>
